Kareem Abdul Hafidzh (Mr.)

Cibubur Country, Cluster Cotton Field, Cotton Field 11 No.7 Mobile: +62 812 7201 303 LinkedIn: Kareem Hafidzh

Email:hafidzhkareem@gmail.com
Github: https://github.com/KareemHafidzh

Profile

A student in BINUS University that interested in Computer Science since in Senior High School, and have made some simple app's like calculator, e-commerse, Portofolio Web, and making NewsApp using Swift for research in Senior High School, and still alot simple app's or web that i've already made, lately studying C/C++, Python, Java, Database in collage.

Education

Vocational Senior High School in SMK IDN - *Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak* **07/2020 – 07/2022**

Focusing Studying about religion and alot programming language, have studied about HTML, CSS, Javascript, Swift, Kotlin, ReactJS, and winning competition 2nd place who made the most video tutorial in first grade, and in my second grade i did an internship in visecoach from December 2021 - August 2022.

Senior High School in SMA Sekolah Alam Cikeas - Ilmu Pengetahuan Alam 07/2022 – 07/2023

In third grade i moved to Senior High School to focusing for collage registration, since i moved i chase up on all the missed material from first - second grade and get average score 77, for the graduation requirement i made research about "tutorial how to make NewsApp in IOS".

Bina Nusantara University - *Software Engineering* **08/2023 – Present**

Currently studying in BINUS University majoring in Software Engineering, and active in organization.

Research Experience

Membuat Aplikasi News App di IOS

02/2023

This research's purpose is to guide people how to make News App with Swift using Xcode, guide the step by step how to make it and explaining the purpose every step.

Internship 2022 – 2023

UI/UX Designer & IOS Developer

trusted to develop design UI of Visecoach App, and trusted to develop programming the design of the Visecoach App.

Assistant Labolatory

2023 – now

Partime

Teaching student's mostly about how to programming and design, and trusted to correction student's answer on lab, also making case for student's final test.

Organization Experience

Panitia Parents Day

2023

Focus on event, trusted to making MC script, event rundown and find a great MC for the event.

Freshmen Leader 2023

Guiding new students about life at binus, leading students in creating projects, and being the major flag bearer at the inauguration

Freshmen Partner 2023 - now

Guiding Student in creating BGA Project, help solve student's campus problem and giving tips how to survive in campus.

Staff Burncup 2023

Making concept for opening and ending event, creating rundown competition during the event, create script mc, and make concept for trailer event.